hey everybody welcome to this english
listening quiz this quiz will test your
listening comprehension skills and will
help you become a better listener but
before we start remember to download the
listening time podcast and if you need
my help to improve your listening then
click on the link in the description
below this video to become a member and
you'll receive my listening practice
seminars which will help you understand
native speakers when they speak fast and
if you become a listening time family
member then you'll get my advanced
podcast episodes where i speak at normal
speed and this will help you reach an
advanced level of listening okay are you
ready for the quiz here's the first
question which of these sentences am i
saying
i want another game
the correct answer is b the word w-o-n
is not pronounced juan it sounds like
this
one and the letter t at the end of the
word want is skipped in this phrase we
say i want another i want another game
alright here's the next question which
of these words am i saying
wheel
the correct answer is a the contraction
of the words we will is not pronounced
wheel it sounds like this wool listen to
this sentence we'll be fine
we don't say we'll be fine we say we'll
be fine okay next question what's the
first word that i'm saying in this
question
what are the options for this
the first word in that question is what
listen again what are the options for
this the phrase what r sounds like this
water what are the options for this all
right last question what sentence am i
saying
it'll help him break out of his shell
write your answer in a comment down
below okay before we go remember to
download the listening time podcast and
click on the link in the description
below this video to become a listening
time member and you'll receive my
listening training which will help you
understand fast english and if you want
my advanced podcast episodes then become
a listening time family member also
remember to subscribe to the channel
click on the bell and follow us on
instagram i'll see you in the next
listening quiz
[Music]